# shahria khan



sayhi@shah-riar.com



linkedin.com/in/shahriakhan



+8801308222365



https://www.shah-riar.com

### Summary

Peace be upon you! My name is Shahria Jaman Khan. I am from a beautiful small town name Jhalakati in Bangladesh. With the experience of Graphic designing and web development, I started my first company DigitalGarage.space in 2020. Primarily this company serves with web development and design. Secondly I am a content creator. To me, the best way to learn something is by sharing. I publish significant things that I learn. Third, I am working to create a company that will bring advancement to technologies of rural farming in Bangladesh.

## **Experience**

### Full-Stack Web Developer

Digital Garage

Jun 2019 - Present (1 year 6 months +)

Full Stack Development.

Website: https://digitalgarage.space

Node.Js, HTML, CSS, Wordpress, MySQL, PHP, Bootstrap, Git

# **Security Officer**

Solaric Global

Jul 2018 - Feb 2019 (8 months)

#### **Education**



## 🔊 Jhalokathi Technical School & College, Jhalokathi

Diploma, Graphic Design

2019 - 2019

Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Photoshop, Microsoft Office

## Jhalokathi Government College, Jhalokathi

High School Diploma, Science

2015 - 2017



#### Jhalokathi Government High School, Jhalokathi

science

2007 - 2015

#### **Licenses & Certifications**



Managing Your Time - LinkedIn

### National Skill Certificate-1 in Graphic Design, NTVQF Level-1 - Bangladesh

**Technical Education Board** Issued May 2019 - Expires May 2024 14109234119000005

- in HTML Essential Training LinkedIn
- in Introduction to CSS LinkedIn
- Google Analytics Individual Qualification Google Digital Academy (Skillshop) Issued Apr 2020 - Expires Apr 2021 49181493
- BYLCX Critical Thinking for Professional Success BYLCX 36027

#### **Skills**

Life Skills • Personal Development • Time Management • Writing • Web Design • Web Development • Graphic Design • Front-end Development • HTML • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)